filedownloads.org 2012-11-16

# FileDownloads.org - Free File Hosting - Easy way to share your files

### Privacy Policy

This policy covers how we use your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information. Any personal information received will only be used to fill your order. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone. 

1\. The following information is collected during rendering services FileDownloads.org confidential and undisclosed unless stated otherwise: 

**1.1. IP addresses.**

IP address of your browser is detected due to the use of Internet-protocols. Such IP address is stored by FileDownloads.org servers for internal use (usage registration, optimal downloads use, statistics etc.); 

**1.2. E-mail.**  
FileDownloads.org servers store and sort user e-mails for the purposes of registration and statistics. FileDownloads.org does not lease, sell, or provide your e-mails to any third parties; 

**1.3. Cookies use.**  
You explicitly authorize FileDownloads.org to create and store cookies at your web-client. Such cookies are exclusively used for your comfort in order to save the browser settings. FileDownloads.org does not use any methods for tracking users (the so-called "spy" or "1x1" gif images etc.); 

**1.4. Safe operation.**  
We have taken the security measures at the server's physical location to protect from loss, incorrect usage, or change of information provided to us by the users of the service. Files, saved at the servers of FileDownloads.org can be accessible only to FileDownloads.org staff members or via a URL initially provided to the uploader. Any files saved by our service are deleted (I) after a certain term of disuse; (II) for violation of User agreement, its supplemental agreements or any applicable legislation; or (III) deleted via a special URL initially provided to the uploader. 

**1.5. Credit card information.**  
Any financial transfers between you and FileDownloads.org are handled by third party, payment services. Your payment details are disclosed to such third parties for the aim of completion of each transaction. The security and non-disclosure of such information is handled by such third parties under their current policies. FileDownloads.org does not sort or store numbers or any information related to your banking card. 

**1.6. Advertisers' access to information.**  
Advertisements located on our website can be posted and/or hosted by a third party, advertisers or their agents. These persons can use the information regarding your visits obtained due to common use of Internet-protocols (geographical location, IP, language and other information automatically disclosed by your browser) to place an advertisement of goods and services that might be interest you. Any information collected at the pages owned by third parties is not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

**2\. DISCLOSURE.**  
FileDownloads.org MAY DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN CASE IT BECOMES NECESSARY TO DEFEND ITS JURIDICAL RIGHTS. IN CASE YOU ACTIONS LEAD TO SUSPICION OF TANGIBLE OR ASSUMED SABOTEUR ACTIONS OR POSES A POTENTIAL THREAT TO ANY PERSON'S PHYSICAL SAFETY OR ANY OTHER GRAVE CRIME, ALL YOUR KNOWN INFORMATION (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PERSONAL DETAILS, IP ADDRESSES, PAYMENT DATA) MAY BE DISCLOSED TO LAW ENFORCEMENT ORGANIZATIONS AND/OR MEMBERS OF THE ISP WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE. IN CASE OF ANY EVIDENCE OF DISTRIBUTION OF THE FILES CONTAINING MATERIALS WHICH APPEAR INVOLVING CHILD EXPLOITATION, THE ACCOUNT BELONGING TO THE USER WHO UPLOADED SUCH FILES WILL BE IMMEDIATELY DELETED AND ALL KNOWN INFORMATION (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PERSONAL DETAILS, IP ADDRESSES, PAYMENT DATA) WILL BE DIRECTED TO THE NATIONAL CENTER FOR MISSING & EXPLOITED CHILDREN, AS WELL AS LAW ENFORCEMENT ORGANIZATIONS AND/OR MEMBERS OF THE ISP WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION CAN BE LAWFUL AS A RESULT OF A LEGAL PROCESS. 

**FileDownloads.org is fully compliant to the DMCA process and any removal requests.**

© 2012 FileDownloads.org - Free File Hosting, All Rights Reserved.
